winbond.com.tw 2019-05-12

# Winbond - Privacy Policy

WINBOND ELECTRONICS CORPORAITON and its affiliates (collectively referred as “We” or “WINBOND”) respect and protect your personal information and this Privacy Statement will help you to understand what data we collect, why we collect and how we protect your personal information.

This Privacy Statement applies to all website or online application that refer to or link to this Privacy Statement.

### Collection of Personal Information

You may be required to provide personal information or others may provide your personal information to us, such as name, address, email address, phone number or other contact information by registering a website account in order to use certain services, to locate product information, to purchase products/services, or to seek assistance at this Website. You may choose whether or not to provide certain personal information to us; however, if you do not provide some required personal information, you may not be able to use or obtain the products/services on this Website. In addition, when you visit our website, we may collect certain personal information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. The personal information we collect in this manner includes IP address, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our website, and dates and times of website visits.

### Purpose of Processing Personal Information

Any personal information WINBOND collects from you or others is used to respond to your inquiries, to send you materials and products, to provide services you request, to provide after-sales service related to the products or services, to provide you with information about products or services, promotions, special offers and other information related to our products or services, to provide you with personalized experience in using this Website, to maintain or upgrade the quality of this Website and the services provided at this Website, or to assess and analyze our market, users, customers, products and services (collectively the “Purpose”).

### Sharing of Information

WINBOND will not release your personal information to any irrelevant third party; however, we may provide such information to WINBOND’s affiliates, contractors, distributors or agents to the extent necessary to carry out the Purpose.

WINBOND also reserves the right to disclose such information to a third party if WINBOND considers any of the following conditions to exist: (1) such disclosure is required by law; (2) such disclosure is required to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (3) such disclosure is to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offences or attacks on the website; (4) such disclosure is required to protect the rights, property, or safety of WINBOND and the users of this Website; or (5) such disclosure would serve to protect public interest.

### International Transfer

We may transfer personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the personal information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the personal information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that personal information as described in this Privacy Statement to offer an adequate level of data protection.

### Exercise the Rights

You may exercise the following rights: (1) rights of inquiry and request for a review of the personal information; (2) rights to make requests for duplications; (3) rights to make supplements or corrections(rectification); (4) rights to request discontinuation or restriction of collection, processing or use of personal information; (5) rights to request deletion of personal information; (6) rights to withdraw your consent any times; (7) rights of data portability; and (8) rights to lodge your complaint ("Exercise the Rights"). WINBOND may not take action, however, on your request for exercising your right, if the applicable law stipulates WINBOND is entitled not to do so. Any exercise of your rights as listed above will result in your not being able to purchase or obtain products or services from WINBOND, to the extent that the Purposes specified herein cannot be attained.

### The Retention of Personal Information

You agree that WINBOND may process and use your personal information via proper means in Taiwan, R.O.C. and other countries within the Purposes specified above, and that WINBOND may retain your personal information (i) only for as long as is considered necessary for the Purpose for which it was collected (including as required by applicable law or regulation), (ii) until you withdraw your consent for us to do so, or (iii) until WINBOND ceases to provide products and services to you. However, where WINBOND is required by mandatory law to retain your personal information or where your personal information is required for WINBOND to assert or defend against legal claims, WINBOND will retain your personal information until the end of the relevant retention period or until the claims in question have been settled.

### Use of Cookies

This Website may send a cookie (a small text file) to your computer in order to facilitate your use of this Website. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may reset your Internet browser to block all cookies. You may also configure your Internet browser so that you receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To learn more about cookies, you may visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)

The WINBOND web server automatically records information incidental to your use of this Website, including but not limited to the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access this Website, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to this Website. WINBOND uses the aforementioned information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout this Website.

### Security

WINBOND will apply appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure the security of your personal information and to avoid your personal information be destructed, lost or unauthorized disclosed or access.

### Children's Privacy

We do not direct this website to nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under 20 (“children’s personal information”).Children under the age of 20 are specifically requested to NOT provide any personal information through this website.If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us at [privacy@winbond.com](mailto:privacy@winbond.com). If we become aware that a child under 20 has provided us with personal information, we take commercially reasonable steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

### Contact

If you have any questions, problems or wish to Exercise the Rights, you may send your information to the following email (contact the persons below).

Please contact us at [privacy@winbond.com](mailto:privacy@winbond.com) .

To reflect of the update regulations or security technologies, WINBOND reserves the right to revise this Privacy Statement at any time.
